Hello,
Здравствуйте
I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky, Ukraine,
я из города Хмельницкий Украина Вы
where do
откуда
I see the city of Moscow from Russia,
я вижу из России город
so let it be there are other options
что так пусть будет есть другие варианты
and also
а также
come from Moscow, live in Moscow
родом из Москвы живёте в Москве
[music]
[музыка]
a few
несколько
No, they go to the Volan family,
Нет они ходят воланскую семейству
not quite Circassians This is Adygea Who shouted there
не совсем черкесы Вот это Адыгее Кто там
I go to Bulgaria,
я Болгарии
they even have a new network in the language with the
они у них даже нового сети на язык с
Circassians are not connected now I’ll look at the
черкесами не связаны сейчас посмотрю
Ossetian language of course it’s interesting
осетинский язык конечно интересно
70 peoples they don’t understand each other at all
70 народов они друг друга вообще не
that they are all there
понимают что они там все эти один
once I hear Ossetians
раз слышу чтобы осетины
deduct that this applies Ossetians are not there
вычитали что это относится осетины нет
but
но
Ossetians are not included there  Ossetians
осетин туда не входят осетины
Ossetian The language is included This is the Iranian
осетинский Язык входит Вот это иранская
group of the Indo-Iranian branch of languages, that is,
группа индоиранской ветви языков то есть
completely different than the Circassian
совсем другая чем Черкесская
Ossetians, so the Circassians are not at all
осетины так черкесами вообще не
related peoples
родственные народы
your ancestors in North Ossetia where did you
ваши предки в Северной Осетии откуда
come from
попали
where do you know
откуда вы знаете
so I look at the Circassians in North
так Я вот смотрю черкесы в Северной
Ossetia I don’t see I
Осетии не вижу
can’t eat any  the settlements may
не может есть какие-то поселения может
have been
были
just Circassian used to occupy a vast
просто черкесие раньше занимал огромную
territory where Sochi is also where
территорию там где Сочи также где вот
these all sorts of Tuapse were all Circassian
эти всякие Туапсе все было черкесские
lands then before the conquest of Russia, but how do
земли потом до завоевания России а как
you feel about the fact that Russia once
вы относитесь к тому что Россия когда-то
your ancestors for the genocide of
ваших предков за геноциде
the legs
ноги
now lives more Circassians than on
сейчас живет больше черкесов чем на
Circassian lands  in Russia
черкесских землях в России
[music]
[музыка]
and now how do you feel about you are not
а сейчас как вы относитесь к вы не
against Ukraine
против Украины
Well, with his bitterness, who is to blame for the fact that
Ну а с горечь его кто виноват в том что
this war is going on,
это война идет
you know
знаете
[music] the
[музыка]
Russian person the topic is good that the
русский человек тема хорош что на себе
right opinion will grieve on yourself First of all,
прискорбьет верного мнения В первую
what else have we done
очередь я еще что мы сделали
also without removing responsibility
также не снимая ответственности
without long references there who is to blame
без долгих там отсылок кто виноват
[music] it
[музыка]
turns out Ukraine is to blame that Russia
получается Украина виновата что Россия
attacked Ukraine
напал на Украину
hostilities where
боевые действия где
[music] the
[музыка]
territory of Ukraine That is, it turns out,
территории Украины То есть получается
as far as I remember Yes, on April 12,
смотрите насколько я помню Да 12 апреля
14, Russian terrorists are the same
14 года российские террористы тот же там
shooters there that you have  now arrested
стрелков которые у вас сейчас арестованы
and invaded the territory of the Donetsk
да вторглись на территорию Донецкой
region, the datalists began hostilities there.
области даталисты начали там боевые
What do you
действия Что
know such shooters girkim on April 12,
знаете такой стрелков гирьким 12 апреля
14, he still
14 года он еще
when he was
когда он был
formally not working
формально не работает
Ukraine hostilities began on
Украина боевые действия начались на 12
April 12 when
апреля когда
tell me if you were not
скажи давай если ты не был
super we found a person who finally
супер мы нашли человека который наконец
the first in all these years to say who
первый за все эти года скажет кто же
started the hostilities before April 12, 14
начал боевые действия до 12 апреля 14
now we will all hear this secret
года сейчас мы все услышим это тайное
Revelation None of the Russians None of the
Откровение Никто из россиян Никто из
people in the Donbass could tell me this
людей на Донбассе не мог мне это сказать
And now we will Let me wait right
А сейчас мы будем Давайте я жду вот
now for the audience just you will say  when the
сейчас зрителям как раз вы скажете когда
hostilities began in the Donbass
начались боевые действия на Донбассе
I’m now on the stream you actually found
Я сейчас на стриме реально вы нашли
the first person who can
первого человека который сможет нам
prove to us that there were hostilities before
доказать что были боевые действия до
1914 no one knows at all no one
1914 года никто вообще не знает никто
even the shooters themselves don’t know
даже сам стрелков не знаю
that there were hostilities before 124
что были боевые действия до 124 года
Come on Show me now I crap
Давай Покажите я сейчас обосрался
like this  all these spoons
вот так эти все ложки
star anything a star when the
звездят что угодно звезда когда
victory is crying an attempt to run away a little Look
плачет перемога попытка чуток убежал
You now on the stream could
Посмотри Ты сейчас на стриме мог всем
try to tell all the viewers Look I am the first
зрителям попытка сказать Смотри я первый
first Russian who dug up this
первый россиянин который откопал эти
secret knowledge not in the history books of the DPR  it’s
тайные знания не в учебниках истории ДНР
autumn right at a time and the ass is
килограмм прям за раз осень а попок
more and more important YouTube driving us
дуже и дуже важен YouTube загоняя нас
through quarries into shadow bans and
через карьерки в теневые бан и дуже
Bogotol’s mind is not shown to people in
Боготол виду не показывается людям в
private information about
частном показывается информация про
streams is shown in order to have a little operational
стримы для того чтобы мало оперативный
whistle, prefer it right at a time and the butt is
свисток предпочтите прям за раз а попок
there in a kilogram okrim video
там в килограмме окрим видео
information and  we are with you
информация и мы с вами
[music]
[музыка]